ZAIN ALABDEEN KHARTABIL

Web Developer



ABOUT ME

Creative and forward-thinking with history building cutting edge websites and applications with challenging demands and visions. with 4+ years of experience in developing and designing web applications and managing databases.

🔀 zainkhartabel1995@gmail.com

+40 791 434 445

linkedin.com/in/zain-alabdeenkhartabil-662019192

https://zainkhartabel.github.io/

LANGUAGES

Romanian O O O

EDUCATION

BSc in Information Technology Engineering (2021)

Damascus University

Software & Information Systems Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Sham Innovation SRL

Full Stack Web Developer 11/2020 - 12/2021 Bucharest, Romania

C#, .Net Core & .Net 5
MSSQL Server & Entity Framework
Blazor
HTML, CSS, SASS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

Orbits Ideal Solutions

Full Stack Web Developer 10/2019 - 10/2020 Damascus, Syria

C#, .Net Framework & .Net Core MSSQL Server ,MySQL & Entity Framework HTML, CSS, Javascript , Bootstrap & Jquery

MY SKILLS







Java Script







COURSES

BIG DATA ANALYTICS: OPPORTUNITIES, CHALLENGES, AND THE FUTURE (3/2021)
Griffith University

VOLUNTEERING

IT Support (8/2015 - 12/2018)

Damascus University

Maintenance of laboratories in the faculty of Information Technology Engineering

HOBBIES









Reading

Football

Swimming

Music